[{"question": "  that\u0092s like the tenth time i\u0092ve peed since i\u0092ve been here!", "answer": " that\u0092s also like the tenth time you told us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " yeah, oh i\u0092m sorry, it must be really hard to hear! i tell ya, it\u0092s a lot easier having three babies play bringing in the noise, bringing in da funk on your bladder! i\u0092m so sick of being pregnant! the only happiness i get is from a cup of coffee, which of course is decaf, \u0091cause\u0097oh! i\u0092m pregnant!", "answer": " pheebs, did\u009ayou want a cookie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  thank you so much.", "answer": " so uh, pheebs, honey, how are those mood swings coming?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey guys!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " all right, here\u0092s the ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  yes! yes! a thousand times, yes!", "answer": " so uh, any ideas for the bachelor party yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa! before you start handing out wedding rings and planning bachelor parties, don\u0092t you have to decide who your best man is gonna be?", "answer": " oh, it\u0092s awkward. it\u0092s awkward. it\u0092s awkward.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i sort\u0092ve already asked chandler.", "answer": " what?! he got to do it at your first wedding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " joey, i figured you\u0092d understand. i mean, i-i\u0092ve known him a lot longer.", "answer": " come on ross! look, i-i don\u0092t have any brothers; i\u0092ll never get to be a best man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " you can be the best man when i get married.", "answer": "  i\u0092ll never get to be a best man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  wait-wait, so, you get to be my best man twice and i never get to be yours at all?", "answer": " oh no-no-no, you\u0097yeah, of course you get to be my best man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  what about me?! you-you just said i could!", "answer": " i\u0092m not even getting married! okay, this is a question for science fiction writers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe you\u0092re not picking me.", "answer": " hey, how can it not be me?!heyhey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i\u0092m not even\u009a i\u0092m not even\u009a", "answer": " fine, y\u0092know what, that\u0092s it. from now on, joey, i want you to be my best man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  stop it!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " one of the babies is kicking.", "answer": " i thought that was a good thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " it\u0092s not kicking me, it\u0092s kicking one of the other babies. oh ! don\u0092t make me come in there!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " do you guys have like a big bowl i can borrow?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " yeah, there\u0092s one right under the cabinet.", "answer": "  thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " why do you need it?", "answer": " oh, we\u0092re having a big party tomorrow night. later!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " whoa! hey-hey, you planning on inviting us?", "answer": " nooo, later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " hormones!", "answer": " what phoebe meant to say was umm, how come you\u0092re having a party and we\u0092re not invited?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh, it\u0092s ross\u0092s bachelor party.", "answer": " sooo?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " are you bachelors?", "answer": " nooo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " are you strippers?", "answer": " nooo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " all right fine! you\u0092re not invited to the party we\u0092re gonna have either.", "answer": " oh-whoa, what party?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " well umm\u009a", "answer": " the baby shower for phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " this is what i\u0092ve got going for the party so far, liquor wise. get a lot of liquor.", "answer": " great. great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " okay, now uh, in terms of the invite list, i\u0092ve got you, me, and chandler and i\u0092m gonna invite gunther \u0091cause, well, we\u0092ve been talking about this pretty loud.", "answer": " i\u0092ll be there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " all right\u0097oh! listen, i know this is your party, but i\u0092d really like to the number of museum geeks that are gonna be there.", "answer": " yeah. tell ya what, let\u0092s not invite any of the anthropologists, only the dinosaur dudes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay! we\u0092ll need a six-pack of zima.", "answer": "  hey guys, what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh, just planning my bachelor party with my best man.", "answer": " yeah, well, good luck trying to top the last one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yeah, see, i don\u0092t think it\u0092s gonna that difficult considering this one won\u0092t be taking place in the basement of a pizza hut.", "answer": " oh, i\u0092m ross. i\u0092m ross. i\u0092m too good for the hut; i\u0092m too good for the hut.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " look, i gotta go pick up ben. everything so far sounds great joey, just remember to keep it on the mellow side, okay? just a couple of guys hanging out playing poker, no-no strippers or anything okay?", "answer": " you got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " okay, see ya later.", "answer": " see ya.  have fun planning your mellow bachelor party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " well, there\u0092s gonna be strippers there. he didn\u0092t say anything about no strippers.", "answer": " he just said, \"no strippers.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " look what i got! look what i got! look what i got!  can you believe they make these for little people?", "answer": " little village people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh, that is so sweet!", "answer": " i know! phoebe is gonna love dressing them in these!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " huh. except, phoebe\u0092s not gonna be the one that gets to dress them.", "answer": " because she\u0092s not gonna get to keep the babies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh my god! we are throwing the most depressing baby shower ever!", "answer": " wait a minute! unless, we give her all gifts she can use after she\u0092s done being pregnant. like-like umm, regular coffee, tequila.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh, and somebody can get those leather pants she\u0092s always wanted!", "answer": " oh, she\u0092s gonna love that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " what the hell is this?! what, did you actually thought it would make me feel better to give me stuff that i can\u0092t use for another two months?! this sucks! all right, what\u0092s my next present?!", "answer": " i don\u0092t have anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " hey listen man, about the stripper\u009a", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " good call!", "answer": "  okay, a little announcement, a little announcement. i\u0092ve decided that my best man is, my best friend gunther!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " what\u0092s my last name?", "answer": " central perk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey-hey, what are those?", "answer": " oh, little party favours, check it out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " wow! yeah!", "answer": " oh-oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  okay, okay, a little announcement, i just want everyone to know that the position of my best man is still open! and uh,  so is the position of the bride.", "answer": " great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " smooth man. yeah, you got some chilie on your neck.  well, i just want to say, thanks everyone, this-this was great. and hey! see you guys monday morning.  thanks joey.", "answer": " oh, hey, don\u0092t forget your shirt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay, hey, museum geeks, party\u0092s over. okay. wave bye-bye to the nice lady. there you go. back to your parent\u0092s basement. all right.  come on boys, come on out! here you go. all right.", "answer": " ohhh, look at the little birdies! are those yours?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " wow, i didn\u0092t know they let you keep chickens and ducks as pets.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " you are really good at that. so uh, i had fun tonight, you throw one hell of a party.", "answer": " oh thanks. thanks. it was great meetin\u0092 ya. and listen if any of my friends gets married, or have a birthday, or a tuesday\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " yeah, that would be great. so i guess umm, good night.", "answer": " oh unless you uh, you wanna hang around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah. i\u0092ll let you play with my duck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  the stripper stole the ring!! the stripper stole the ring!! chandler! chandler, get up! get up! the stripper stole the ring!", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " the ring is gone!", "answer": " ugh. just a sec, give me a minute to wake up for this\u0097ah-ha-ha!! you lost the ring! you\u0092re the worst best man ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " dude, this isn\u0092t funny! what am i gonna do?! i go to bed last night, everything\u0092s cool! i wake up this morning, the stripper\u0092s gone and the ring is gone!", "answer": " you slept with the stripper?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hi, guys.", "answer": " hi! phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " hi phoebe.", "answer": " i-i wanted to apologise if i\u0097y\u0092know seemed a tad edgy yesterday at my shower. y\u0092know it\u0092s just the hormones, y\u0092know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no we\u009a", "answer": " hormones.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " \u009ahormones, yeah.", "answer": " anyway, i just wanted to say thank you, it was just, it was so sweet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " wow, you seem to be doing so much better. that\u0092s great. so how-how are things going?", "answer": " good. y\u0092know\u0097no-no, okay, it\u0092s-it feels like everything\u0092s been about me lately, so what\u0092s happening with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh, well, actually we were just talking about me not going to ross\u0092s wedding.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " it just might be too hard, given the history and all that\u009a", "answer": " wow! this reminds me of the time when i was umm, living on the street and this guy offered to buy me food if i slept with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well, h-how is this like that?", "answer": " well, let\u0092s see, it\u0092s not. really, like that. because, you see that was an actual problem, and uh, yours is just like y\u0092know a bunch of y\u0092know high school crap that nobody really gives y\u0092know\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  i\u0092m-i\u0092m sorry, i just thought that\u009a", "answer": " alrighty, here come the water works.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " ugh! i don\u0092t know what i\u0092m going to do! i called the company that sent and th-they don\u0092t care! then i called 9-1-1 and they laughed at me, if this isn\u0092t an emergency, then what is?", "answer": "  hey guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i just wanted to thank you again for last night, what a great party! and the guys from work had a blast. y\u0092know, one of them had never been to a bachelor party before. yeah! and-and another one had never been to a party before, so\u009a", "answer": " so uh, hey, that uh, that wedding ring, huh? man, that\u0092s nice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " yeah, right!", "answer": " i was uh, i was thinking i might want to pick one of those babies up for myself, i might want to get one of those\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " that ring? when my grandmother first came to this country, that ring and the clothes on her back were all she had with her.", "answer": " so you might say, the ring is irreplaceable?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh absolutely! it has been in my family for generations, and every bride who has worn it has had a long and happy life.", "answer": " so you might say, it\u0092s a magic ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  yeah, the stripper stole it.", "answer": " my-my ring? my-my wedding ring? the-the stripper stole my wedding ring?! h-how?! how could this all happen?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well, i think it all started when you said, \"hey joey, why don\u0092t you be my best man.\"", "answer": "  all right-all right, fine! i-i\u0092m gonna call the cops!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " dude, i screwed up, you don\u0092t have to turn me in!", "answer": " not on you! on the stripper!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh, yeah, well i already did that! they said they\u0092re gonna look into it right after they solved all the murders.", "answer": " okay, well, we\u0092ll call the company that sent her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " i did that too! they wouldn\u0092t give me her real name or her number. they said, \"if i bothered them again they\u0092d call the police.\" i said, \"if you talk to the police, you tell them i\u0092m missing a ring!\"", "answer": " so what, joey? wh-wh-what? what are you telling me? that there\u0092s nothing we can do? well, how could this happen?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " look ross, i am so-so sorry. i-i-i\u009a", "answer": " well, what if we just ah, called her, used a fake name, and had her come to my office?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  it\u0092s so good.  oh, thanks.", "answer": " good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " i\u0092m so glad you liked it.", "answer": "  oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " what?! she made the tea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh! no, i-i think i just had a contraction.", "answer": " you what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " yeah, i thought i had one a couple of minutes ago, and now i know that was definitely one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " wait, you can\u0092t have the baby here! i mean i haven\u0092t sterilised it since the guys moved out!", "answer": " okay. it\u0092s okay. we\u0092re gonna be okay. y\u0092know what? it\u0092s okay. i\u0092m gonna, i\u0092m gonna, i\u0092m gonna boil some water and just rip up some sheets!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " no. it\u0092s all right; it\u0092s probably false labour. they said that, that can happen near the end, just somebody get the book.", "answer": " rachel, get the book! the book!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " okay!  okay! here!", "answer": " the bible?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " all right, okay, this is great, uh, chandler, you get behind the desk. and-and when she comes in hopefully, she won\u0092t recognise you because, well, why would she? uh, okay, and then you buzz ross and i.  you be mr. gonzalez, and i\u0092ll be uh, mr. wong.", "answer": " diverse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " did anybody call for security?", "answer": "  you be cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay, which one of you guys is gunther central-perk?  hey, joey?", "answer": " where\u0092s my ring? my dead grandmother\u0092s wedding ring? where is it? where is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " way to be cool, man.", "answer": " what\u0092s he talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " there was a ring, in a box, on my nightstand, after you left, it was gone!", "answer": " wait, you guys think i stole some ring?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " we know you took so just-just save yourself the time and confess!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " okay, who are you? the hardy boys? look, i don\u0092t need to steal some stupid ring, all right? i make $1,600 a week doing what i do; any of you guys make that?", "answer": " marry me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i still don\u0092t get how you know when it\u0092s false labour.", "answer": " well, do you see any babies?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " how do you feel?", "answer": " okay, i guess. i mean\u009a i don\u0092t know, it\u0092s just, i guess i know it\u0092s going to be over soon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " well, isn\u0092t that a good thing? you said you were sick of this.", "answer": " i know. it\u0092s just y\u0092know usually when you\u0092re, when you\u0092re done with the pregnant thing, y\u0092know, then you get to do the mom thing. i\u0092m gonna be y\u0092know, sitting around in my leather pants, drinking tequila.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " some moms do that.", "answer": " okay that\u0092s even sadder. look, i know, i know what i got myself into, it\u0092s just that now that they\u0092re in me it\u0092s like, it\u0092s like i know them y\u0092know, i mean-i mean, it\u0092s just not gonna be easy when these little babies have to go away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " aww, sweetie, but it\u0092s not like you\u0092re not gonna have anything. you\u0092re gonna have nieces and nephews, and some ways that\u0092s even better.", "answer": " yeah, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " no, really. really, pheebs, you\u0092re not gonna be the one worrying about saving for college, or yelling at them when they\u0092re bad, y\u0092know, or deciding to put them on ritalin when they just won\u0092t calm down. y\u0092know?", "answer": " i mean, you\u0092re the one they\u0092re gonna come to when they wanna run away from home, and the one they talk to about sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " and you just get to be cool aunt phoebe!", "answer": " cool aunt phoebe. i am pretty cool!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " and y\u0092know what else, oh my god, are they gonna love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " they are gonna love me.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " thanks you guys! again.", "answer": " oh, sweetie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " you\u0092re the best. thanks. oh! monica and rachel: what?!", "answer": " just kidding. ahh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " if anything should happen to him\u009a", "answer": " joey! the vet said it\u0092s a simple procedure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " so! things can go wrong! you don\u0092t know! what if he doesn\u0092t make it?!", "answer": " he will, joe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i\u0092m so worried about him, y\u0092know?", "answer": "  somebody lose a ring?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " h-h-h-how\u0092s the duck?", "answer": " he\u0092s doing just fine, he\u0092s resting now, but you can see him in a little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " ohh, great! oh hey, listen ross, thanks for being so cool about this.", "answer": " no, that\u0092s all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s not. i mean you-you made me your best man and i totally let you down!", "answer": " hey, come on, it\u0092s not your fault.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " yeah, it is! you wouldn\u0092t have lost the ring, right? y\u0092know what, ross you were right from the start, he  should be your best man.", "answer": " no, you should.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " now, don\u0092t argue with me\u009a", "answer": " hey! hey! hey! i get to choose my best man, and i want both you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " thanks man.", "answer": "  i gotta go check something over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " what a baby.", "answer": " total wuss!  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}]